export default {
  id: 'low_1006_6_1b',
  name: '상용한자(6학년-1/한자찾기)',
  data: [
    { question: '독:きざ(む)/음:こく', answer: ['刻'] },
    { question: '독:집/음:かく', answer: ['閣'] },
    { question: '독:ほ(す)、ひ(る)/음:かん', answer: ['干'] },
    { question: '독:볼/음:かん', answer: ['看'] },
    { question: '독:대쪽/음:かん', answer: ['簡'] },
    { question: '독:はがね/음:こう', answer: ['鋼'] },
    { question: '독:お(りる)、お(ろす)、ふ(る)/음:こう', answer: ['降'] },
    { question: '독:はげ(しい)/음:げき', answer: ['激'] },
    { question: '독:きぬ/음:けん', answer: ['絹'] },
    { question: '독:うやま(う)/음:けい', answer: ['敬'] },
    { question: '독:경계할/음:けい', answer: ['警'] },
    { question: '독:とど(ける)、とど(く)/음:かい', answer: ['届'] },
    { question: '독:맬/음:けい', answer: ['系'] },
    { question: '독:곡식/음:こく', answer: ['穀'] },
    { question: '독:こま(る)/음:こん', answer: ['困'] },
    { question: '독:ほね/음:こつ', answer: ['骨'] },
    { question: '독:そな(える)、とも/음:きょう、く', answer: ['供'] },
    { question: '독:권세/음:けん、ごん', answer: ['権'] },
    { question: '독:ま(く)、まき/음:かん', answer: ['巻'] },
    { question: '독:つくえ/음:き', answer: ['机'] },
    { question: '독:とうと(い)、とうと(ぶ)、たっと(い)、たっと(ぶ)/음:き', answer: ['貴'] },
    { question: '독:심할/음:げき', answer: ['劇'] },
    { question: '독:つと(める)、つと(まる)/음:きん、ごん', answer: ['勤'] },
    { question: '독:すじ/음:きん', answer: ['筋'] },
    { question: '독:おのれ/음:こ、き', answer: ['己'] },
    { question: '독:あたた(か)、あたた(かい)、あたた(まる)、あたた(める)/음:だん', answer: ['暖'] },
    { question: '독:むずか(しい)、かた(い)/음:なん', answer: ['難'] },
    { question: '독:おさ(める)、おさ(まる)/음:のう、なっ、な、なん、とう', answer: ['納'] },
    { question: '독:골/음:のう', answer: ['脳'] },
    { question: '독:층계/음:だん', answer: ['段'] },
    { question: '독:かつ(ぐ)、にな(う)/음:たん', answer: ['担'] },
    { question: '독:무리/음:とう', answer: ['党'] },
    { question: '독:엿/음:とう', answer: ['糖'] },
    { question: '독:みだ(れる)、みだ(す)/음:らん', answer: ['乱'] },
    { question: '독:볼/음:らん', answer: ['覧'] },
    { question: '독:たまご/음:らん', answer: ['卵'] },
    { question: '독:ほが(らか)/음:ろう', answer: ['朗'] },
    { question: '독:논할/음:ろん', answer: ['論'] },
    { question: '독:법칙/음:りつ、りち', answer: ['律'] },
    { question: '독:うら/음:り', answer: ['裏'] },
    { question: '독:のぞ(む)/음:りん', answer: ['臨'] },
    { question: '독:장막/음:まく、ばく', answer: ['幕'] },
    { question: '독:늦을/음:ばん', answer: ['晩'] },
    { question: '독:な(い)/음:ぼう、もう', answer: ['亡'] },
    { question: '독:わす(れる)/음:ぼう', answer: ['忘'] },
    { question: '독:낱/음:まい', answer: ['枚'] },
    { question: '독:맹세/음:めい', answer: ['盟'] },
    { question: '독:く(れる)、く(らす)/음:ぼ', answer: ['暮'] },
    { question: '독:본뜰/음:も、ぼ', answer: ['模'] },
    { question: '독:빽빽할/음:みつ', answer: ['密'] },
    { question: '독:나눌/음:はん', answer: ['班'] },
    { question: '독:おとず(れる)、たず(ねる)/음:ほう', answer: ['訪'] },
    { question: '독:おが(む)/음:はい', answer: ['拝'] },
    { question: '독:せ、せい、そむ(く)、そむ(ける)/음:はい', answer: ['背'] },
    { question: '독:배우/음:はい', answer: ['俳'] },
    { question: '독:なみ、なら(べる)、なら(ぶ)/음:へい', answer: ['並'] },
    { question: '독:あぎな(う)/음:ほ', answer: ['補'] },
    { question: '독:たから/음:ほう', answer: ['宝'] },
    { question: '독:はら/음:ふく', answer: ['腹'] },
    { question: '독:막대/음:ぼう', answer: ['棒'] },
    { question: '독:いな/음:ひ', answer: ['否'] },
    { question: '독:ふる(う)/음:ふん', answer: ['奮'] },
    { question: '독:ひ(める)/음:ひ', answer: ['秘'] },
    { question: '독:비평할/음:ひ', answer: ['批'] },
    { question: '독:わたくし、わたし/음:し', answer: ['私'] },
    { question: '독:すな/음:さ、しゃ', answer: ['砂'] },
    { question: '독:말/음:し', answer: ['詞'] },
    { question: '독:す(てる)/음:しゃ', answer: ['捨'] },
    { question: '독:い(る)/음:しゃ', answer: ['射'] },
    { question: '독:きず、いた(む)、いた(める)/음:しょう', answer: ['傷'] },
    { question: '독:마을/음:しょ', answer: ['署'] },
    { question: '독:よ(い)/음:ぜん', answer: ['善'] },
    { question: '독:베풀/음:せん', answer: ['宣'] },
    { question: '독:しろ/음:じょう', answer: ['城'] },
    { question: '독:も(る)、さか(る)、さか(ん)/음:せい、じょう', answer: ['盛'] },
    { question: '독:성인/음:せい', answer: ['聖'] },
    { question: '독:まこと/음:せい', answer: ['誠'] },
    { question: '독:あら(う)/음:せん', answer: ['洗'] },
    { question: '독:た(れる)、た(らす)/음:すい', answer: ['垂'] },
    { question: '독:おさ(まる)、おさ(める)/음:しゅう', answer: ['収'] },
    { question: '독:나무/음:じゅ', answer: ['樹'] },
    { question: '독:う(れる)/음:じゅく', answer: ['熟'] },
    { question: '독:순수할/음:じゅん', answer: ['純'] },
    { question: '독:볼/음:し', answer: ['視'] },
    { question: '독:われ、わ/음:が', answer: ['我'] },
    { question: '독:わか(い)、も(しくは)/음:じゃく、にゃく', answer: ['若'] },
    { question: '독:おごそ(か)、きび(しい)/음:げん、ごん', answer: ['厳'] },
    { question: '독:지경/음:いき', answer: ['域'] },
    { question: '독:わけ/음:やく', answer: ['訳'] },
    { question: '독:の(びる)、の(べる)、の(ばす)/음:えん', answer: ['延'] }
  ]
}
